moongiant.com 2018-03-18

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Moongiant's purpose is to be an interesting little corner of the internet dedicated to the safe and fun exploration of Astronomy and the Moon. 

Limitation of Liability  
MOONGIANT PROVIDES THE INFORMATION, SERVICES AND PRODUCTS ON THIS WEB SITES "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. MOONGIANT SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE IN ANY MANNER FOR THE ACTS OF ANY THIRD PARTY, INCLUDING WITOUT LIMITATION, ANY THIRD PARTY AD NETWORK. 

Any information we collect is information you provide (such as first name, age, city state and birthday) and will not be shared with a third party. Some data collected may be used seperate from any person information. For example, when you enter your birthday in our birthday moon phase calculator we only keep the birthday and use it with the larger pool of data collected to show how many people are born on a full moon. The birthday is kept as an anonomous date and not attached to any personal information

If you send us artwork, comments or anything else which we post on our site, you will be identified only by first name, age, city and state. If you send us an e-mail with a question or comment, we will write back using your e-mail address, but we will not keep the address or use it again, unless you have a follow-up question.

If you use the "Recommend this site to a Friend" feature, we will ask for your first name and e-mail address as well as the e-mail address of the person who will receive the message. We will only use this information to send the message and we will delete the information when the message is sent.

Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address. IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site for the use of monitoring statistics of the site.

No one will be excluded from our site for not giving us personal information. When we do ask for personal information (like an e-mail address), we will only keep it until that particular activity is complete. We will not share this information with a third party. We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may make a purchase only with involvement of a parent or guardian. 

As you visit Moongiant.com it is possible that several cookies will be set on your computer. Moongiant uses the information from cookies to remember browser preferences, and improve our visitors' experiences on the site. No personal information is ever stored in a Moongiant cookie even if you have entered your name or e-mail address on other parts of Moongiant.

Moongiant does not sell information collected by cookies or use the information for commerce-related purposes. In addition, Moongiant will not filter content based on your preferences without permission.

You should check back to this policy frequently, since it is subject to change from time to time, and your continued use of the site is conditioned upon your acceptance of any modifications hereto. 

If you have any questions or concerns, send us an e-mail at info@Moongiant.com. 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 2012 and supersedes all earlier versions of our Privacy Policy.
